<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Pet Care Application</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password" />
    <string name="Password">Password</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="click_to_login">Click to Login</string>
    <string name="click_to_register">Click to Register</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="Home" />
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="dog_information">Dog Information</string>
    <string name="cat_information">Cat Information</string>
    <string name="set_reminder">Set Reminder</string>
    <string name="dog_pic">dog pic</string>
    <string name="dog_info">Dog Information</string>
    <string name="dog_development">Dog Development</string>
    <string name="dog_dev_one">Stage 1: Neonatal Period (0 – 2 weeks) - This is the first stage of puppy development and begins at birth. At this age, puppies only have the sense of taste and touch and rely totally on their mother.</string>
    <string name="dog_dev_two">Stage 2: Transitional Period (2 – 4 weeks) - Sensory development continues with hearing and sense of smell. Puppy teeth start coming through and their eyes will begin to open. This is also the age where your puppy’s personality begins to develop. Puppies will interact with their litter mates, wag their tails, stand, walk a little and bark.</string>
    <string name="dog_dev_three">Stage 3: Socialization Period (3 – 12 weeks) -Between 3- 5 weeks puppies start to become aware of their surroundings and can develop a relationship with people. At the 7-9 weeks stage, they will have full use of all their senses and will be ready to go home to their new owners. This is a great period to begin crate training.</string>
    <string name="dog_dev_four">Stage 4: Testing Period (3 – 6 months) - At this age your puppy is going to go through teething and chewing is a common side effect. Before your puppy starts chewing on your furniture: Don’t leave him unattended. Make sure he has plenty of chew sticks and toys. Use commercial sprays or gels that dissuade your puppy from chewing your belongings.</string>
    <string name="dog_dev_five">Stage 5: Adolescence (6 – 18 months)- This can be the most difficult time during a puppy’s development – adolescence. Your cute little puppy is becoming a teenager and will start producing hormones which may result in changes in behaviour. Dogs go through adolescence much earlier than people; for small breeds, is can be as early as six months old while larger dogs starting at nine or 10 months of age. Adolescence in larger breed dogs continues until they are two or three years old with smaller dogs reaching maturity at about 18 months. Typically, the larger the dog, the slower the development.</string>
    <string name="dog_diet">Dog Diet</string>
    <string name="dog_diet_info">It is entirely acceptable to feed your dog a pure kibble diet. Or you can mix their diet up with some cooked or raw meat, fish, vegetables, and rice. Many owners like to feed a raw meat diet to their dogs, and while this can suit some dogs very well, there are some important considerations you need to be aware of.</string>
    <string name="dog_training">Dog Training</string>
    <string name="dog_training_info">Your regular grooming routine should include brushing, trimming (including the nails), and bathing. Grooming your dog has many benefits: It keeps their skin and coat shiny and healthy and for dogs with longer hair it can reduce matting that can cause skin problems.</string>
    <string name="dog_home">Home</string>
    <string name="cat_info">Cat Information</string>
    <string name="cat_development">Cat Development</string>
    <string name="cat_dev_one">Kittens (Birth up to 1 year)-Kittens have a very high play drive. Now is the best time for gradual positive introductions to people and other pets. It is also the right time for your cat to become comfortable with nail trims, tooth and coat brushing, their cat carrier, and transportation to the veterinary practice.</string>
    <string name="cat_dev_two">Young Adult (1 year – 6 years)-Inter-cat aggression may develop at this stage of life along with sexual maturity. Be sure to use appropriate play with your cat.</string>
    <string name="cat_dev_three">Mature Adult (7 – 10 years)-Play activity begins to decrease, and your cat becomes more likely to gain weight. Many people assume their cat is young and healthy, but a lot can change in just one cat year which equals four human years. Your cat will benefit from regular check-ups to keep her/him healthy and prevent disease or illnesses.</string>
    <string name="cat_dev_five">Senior (over 10 years)-The human equivalent at the beginning of this life stage is about 60 years. Senior cats may exhibit behavioural changes (e.g., vocalization, changes in litter box usage, not going up and down stairs as easy). Senior cats should visit the veterinarian a minimum of every six months since much could happen in a year and your veterinarian can catch things early on before they are more advanced or costly to treat.</string>
    <string name="cat_diet">Cat Diet</string>
    <string name="cat_diet_info">Cats are obligate carnivores, which means that they rely on nutrients found only in animal products. Cats evolved as hunters that consume prey that contains high amounts of protein, moderate amounts of fat, and a minimal amount of carbohydrates, and their diet still requires these general proportions today.</string>
    <string name="cat_training">Cat Training</string>
    <string name="cat_training_info">Training a cat is not much different than training a dog. By using positive reinforcement training, you\'re simply looking for what your cat finds motivating and what they\'ll work for. For many cats, this will likely be treats in the form of food, but some cats find play or praise incredibly motivating.</string>
    <string name="cat_home">Home</string>
    <string name="cat_pic">cat pic</string>
    <string name="reminder_pic">reminder pic</string>
    <string name="logo">logo</string>
    <string name="logout_pic">logout pic</string>
    <string name="pet_care">Pet Care</string>
    <string name="user_details">User Details</string>
    <string name="reminder_home">reminder home</string>
    <string name="rem_home">Home</string>
    <string name="user_id">User ID</string>
    <string name="set">Set</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
</resources>